

Backend Developer

DOB: 29/03/1995

Phone: 0886886321

Mail: linhvu0395@gmail.com

Website: https://gigglelink.github.io/portfolio



Python Java React JavaScript Microsoft SQL Server HTML CSS

<u>Language</u>

- English : Advanced

Vietnamese : Native

Experience

Lobby Lounge Restaurant Attendant, JW Marriott hotel Hanoi, Vietnam (Bartender, Cashier, Waiter) January 2022 - February 2023

Building and customer services supervisor, Hanoi Property Management (HPM), Hanoi November 2019 - December 2021

Education

Hanoi, Vietnam

FUNIX

(2022 – 2023) Java Developer – degree expected March 2023

- Programming in Java (Java)
- Learn data structure, organizing data (Java)
- Database (SQL Server)
- Web Application Development
- Build responsive websites with HTML and CSS (HTML, CSS)
- Programming with JavaScript (JavaScript)

Lucerne, Switzerland

Swiss Institute for Management and Hospitality (Swiss IM&H) (2014-2018) BBA in Hospitality Management

About

While I was working in the hospitality industry, I was suggested by a friend to switch to programming. After careful consideration and research, I have decided to change my career path.

Since then I have gone through as much material as I can on my own, I also taken programming course at FUNIX for better understanding and a more solid structure.

Programming was intellectually stimulating and exciting for me. I am a logical thinker with endless patience, I love solving problem and always strive to learn more. With programming, it felt like I have discovered my passion in life.